https://www.cropscience.bayer.us/privacy-statement

Privacy Statement
| Crop Science US
Bayer GlobalMediaInvestorsCareerContactSitemapCreate AccountLoginRetailer Portal
HomeCrop ProtectionOverviewFungicidesAbsoluteLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerAbsolute MaxxLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingFAQResourcesAsk BayerAlietteLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingResourcesAsk BayerDelaroLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingFAQResourcesAsk BayerFlint ExtraLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingResourcesAsk BayerGemLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerLunaLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingSummer Almond Disease ControlMovento + Luna for WalnutsScala + Luna in AlmondSpring Almond Disease Risk Resistance ManagementResourcesAsk BayerPrevicur FlexLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingResourcesAsk BayerProlineLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingResourcesAsk BayerPropulseLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingResourcesAsk BayerProsaroLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingSuccess StoriesResourcesFAQApplication TipsAsk BayerProvost SilverLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingTrial DataResourcesAsk BayerReasonLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingResourcesAsk BayerScalaLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingResourcesAsk BayerSerenade ASOLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingResourcesAsk BayerSerenade OptiLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingMedia GalleryResourcesAsk BayerStrategoLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingFAQAsk BayerStratego YLDLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingFAQResourcesSuccess StoriesAsk BayerHarvest Aids / PGRFinish 6 ProLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerGinstarLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingFAQAsk BayerStanceLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerHerbicidesAlionLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingFAQResourcesMedia GalleryAsk BayerAutumn SuperLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingResourcesAsk BayerAxiomLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerBalance FlexxLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingFAQSuccess StoriesMedia GalleryResourcesAsk BayerCaprenoLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingFAQSuccess StoriesMedia GalleryResourcesAsk BayerCorvusLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingFAQSuccess StoriesMedia GalleryResourcesFormula for SuccessAsk BayerDegree XtraLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerDiFlexxLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingResourcesAsk BayerDiFlexx DUOLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingFAQResourcesAsk BayerHarnessLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerHarness MAXLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerHarness XtraLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerHarness Xtra 5.6LLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerHuskieLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerHuskie CompleteLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingResourcesAsk BayerLaudisLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingFAQSuccess StoriesMedia GalleryResourcesLow Use RateAsk BayerLuxxurLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerNortron SCLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerOlympusLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerOspreyLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerRicestar HTLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerRimfire MaxLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingResourcesAsk BayerRoundup PowerMAXLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingResourcesAsk BayerRoundup PowerMAX II Labels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerRoundup PowerMAX 3Labels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingTrial DataAsk BayerRoundup WeatherMAXLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerRT 3Labels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingResourcesAsk BayerTripleFLEX IILabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerVarroLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerWarrantLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerWarrant UltraLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerWolverineLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerWolverine AdvancedLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerXtendiMaxInsecticidesAdmire ProLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingResourcesAsk BayerBaythroid XLLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingResourcesAsk BayerLeverage 360Labels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingResourcesAsk BayerMoventoLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingLuna + Movento in WalnutVelum Prime + MoventoFAQTrial DataResourcesAsk BayerOberonLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingFAQResourcesAsk BayerRequiemLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingResourcesAsk BayerSivantoLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingResourcesAsk BayerVelum OneLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingTrial DataFAQResourcesProtect Your Almonds Against Nematodes with Velum OneAsk BayerVelum PrimeLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingVelum Prime + MoventoTrial DataFAQResourcesProtect Your Potatoes Against Nematodes with Velum PrimeAsk BayerVelum TotalLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsFAQKey PestsUse & MixingResourcesAsk BayerSeedTraitsAll ProductsSeedGrowthOverviewAerisLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingTrial DataFAQSuccess StoriesResourcesAsk BayerAllegianceLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerEmesto SilverLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingResourcesAsk BayerEverGolLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerFluency Agent AdvancedLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsUse & MixingResourcesAsk BayerGaucho 600Labels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerGaucho XTLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerPoncho BetaLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingResourcesAsk BayerRaxilLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingRaxil Pro MDLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingTrial DataRaxil PRO ShieldLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingTrial DataAsk BayerThiramLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerTrilexLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerTrilex AdvancedLabels / MSDSRegistered CropsKey PestsUse & MixingAsk BayerSeed Treatment EquipmentOn DemandEquipment DesignSystem FeaturesCustomer SupportSystem Control PanelFAQCommercial Batch TreatersBasic SystemLoss In Weight SystemUnitized Volumetric SystemsBatch Modular CoaterAccessoriesSales & Support ContactsDownstream Drum TreatersBasic SystemCommercial SystemCF 35 SystemAccessoriesSales & Support ContactsDiscontinued ItemsAsk BayerResource CenterOverviewArticlesResearch and InnovationCalifornia Innovation SeriesRoundup Ready® Xtend Crop System UpdatesBayer Learning CentersCereal ExpertsGrain for Good2018 Grain for Good WinnersApplication ChartGrain Quality SeriesInsights from our Cereal ExpertsGrower InsightsSolutions by RegionToolsBayer PLUS Rewards CalculatorBayer Product Selector ToolReward ProgramsOverviewBayer PLUSBayer PLUS RewardsBayer PLUS Rewards Knowledge Center Terms & ConditionsBayer PLUS CitrusTerms & ConditionsBayer PLUS PotatoTerms & ConditionsBayer PLUS SugarbeetTerms & ConditionsBayer PLUS VegetableTerms & ConditionsBayer PLUS FAQsInnovation Plus ProgramRoundup Ready PLUSWho We AreOverviewOur BusinessOur ValuesOur Locations Sacramento AreaInstituteKansas CityPasadenaShakopeeNews and EventsOur CommitmentOverviewAgVocateBee HealthFood Chain PartnershipGrow OnIntegrated Weed ManagementProduct StewardshipCalifornia Transparency in Supply ChainsUS Roundup SettlementContactCreate AccountLoginRetailer Portal
Home
Privacy Statement
Effective Date: July 1, 2020
We know your privacy is important to you, and our aim with
this Privacy Statement is to help you make informed choices about your personal
data. This Privacy Statement explains what personal data we collect about you,
what we do with it, and how you can control it in connection with our websites,
mobile apps, or other online services (the “Site”). This Privacy Statement also applies to the personal data
we collect through hardcopy means.
You can navigate to any of the sections of this Privacy
Statement using the links below:
Why we collect your information
How long we keep your information
What information we collect about you
How we share your information
Third-party analytics
How you can control your information
How we protect your information
Children’s personal data
The term “personal
data” can have different meanings depending on applicable law. In general, we
use the term “personal data” to mean information that can uniquely identify
you, but we will treat information we collect from you as personal data
wherever necessary under applicable law.
We collect personal data about you for the following
reasons:
For our internal
efforts to operate and improve our business. This could include:
Enabling your use of our services and fulfilling
your requests for certain products and services.
Making the Site or our current products better.
Developing new products or new content for the
Site.
Using the information for internal financial
activities like auditing, billing, and forecasting.
Performing data analysis to identify ways we can
operate more efficiently or expand our business.
Verifying and maintaining the quality and safety
of our products.
For advertising and
marketing purposes. This could include:
Sending you information on promotions or surveys
we offer, or information about us and our events.
Enhancing, personalizing and evaluating the
effectiveness of the content of our Site, our communications with you, and our
advertising and marketing.
For our general
administrative purposes. For example, we may need your information to tell
you about important changes to the Site, manage your registered account, or
provide account credit or other customer service to you. We may also need your
information to administer promotions or programs we offer.
For social-media
engagement. We use social-media
accounts (including Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, Pinterest, and Instagram) to
engage with the public. This engagement allows us to build online awareness
about our company and our products; respond to messages through the comment,
message, or chat functions; collect aggregated information about interactions
with our content; analyze trends; identify and profile brand advocates and key influencers;
and conduct social-media listening of conversations about our company and our
products. When you engage with us through our social-media channels, the
platform providers will also process information about you. For further
information, please consult the privacy policy of the platform provider.
For
security purposes, as necessary to help us protect against, identify, or
investigate fraud or other criminal activity.
For other legal
purposes, if we have a legal obligation, or need to pursue or defend
against legal claims, for which we need to process your information.
For communication
purposes, to get in touch with you in connection with any of the reasons
discussed above.
How long we
keep your information
We will keep your
information for as long as we need it to carry out the purposes described
above, and as necessary to comply with statutory and regulatory retention requirements.
We will also keep your information as necessary to comply with other legal
obligations we may have, such as in connection with litigation.
What information
we collect about you
Information
you provide.  We may collect your
first and last name, email, street address, state, zip code, age, gender,
demographic information, preferences, or other information you voluntarily send
to us through the Site or through communications with us, including when you:
Create
an account
Register
for a service
Subscribe
to a mailing list
Join a
rewards program
Information gathered
automatically. When you visit the Site, we may automatically collect
information directly or through our third-party analytics providers. That
information may include:
Your IP
address
Your
device identifier
Your
internet-service provider’s name
Browser
type and language
Online
browsing data or “clickstream data” (e.g., date and time of access to the
Site, referring website address, pages viewed, features used, links
clicked, and other actions you take in connection with the website)
We (and third parties acting on our behalf) may collect this
information directly from your browser interacting with our Site. We may also
collect it through cookies and similar technologies, which typically work by
placing a small file (like a text file or graphic) on your browser, and the
file is used to identify your device and to collect information. In this
Privacy Statement, we use the term “cookies” in general to refer to these
technologies. Cookies are typically assigned to one of four categories,
depending on their function and intended purpose:
Essential Cookies: These cookies
are necessary for our Site to operate properly and enable you to use its
features.
Performance Cookies: These cookies
collect information about how you use our Site and are used to improve and
personalize future web experiences and deliver content more relevant to
your interests. Our promotional communications may include these cookies to
measure performance and deliver more relevant offers/content based on
preferences.
Functional Cookies: These cookies
allow our Site to remember choices you make and provide more personal
features as well as services you have asked for. The information collected
may be anonymized and is not used to track your browsing activities on
other websites.
Marketing Cookies: We use cookies
to help us deliver our content and advertising. You can find more
information below on advertising, including your choices with respect to
these cookies.
Most browsers are set up to accept cookies automatically.
You can deactivate the storing of cookies or adjust your browser to inform you
before the cookie is stored on your computer. You can find more information
about cookies and how they work at https://www.allaboutcookies.org/.
In the case of third-party cookies for interest-based advertising, you can opt
out of receiving interest-based ads from members of the Digital Advertising
Alliance at http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ for
web properties  or at https://youradchoices.com/appchoices for mobile apps.
Some browsers have “do not track” features that allow you to
tell a website not to track you.  These
features are not all uniform. We do not currently respond to those signals.
Instead, we collect, use, and share information as described in this Privacy
Statement regardless of a “do not track” choice.
Location-based
information. When you access the Site, we may collect information related
to your location through your device’s GPS, Wi-Fi, Bluetooth, or IP address.
Your device may provide ways to prevent sharing your location, like disabling
location-based services or turning off your GPS, Wi-Fi, or Bluetooth. If you
disable any location-based services on your device, you may not be able to use
certain features of the Site.
Information from
social media and other sources. We may collect information about you from
other sources such as our
affiliates, public and third-party databases, and other third parties. For
example, if you elect to participate in analytics, communications, or marketing
programs, including those offered or run by third parties, we may enhance your
information by obtaining or merging that information with technical, cookie, or
other data we collect or that we receive from third parties.
We may collect information when you interact with us through
social media. And if you link our Site with a social media
account, then we may collect certain information related to that account. You
may have the ability to control what information is shared from your linked
social-media account by adjusting the privacy settings for that account.
We also use a third-party
social-listening platform that compiles publicly accessible content on the
internet in order to create aggregate reports that allow us to better understand
our brand categories and more effectively market our products. This publicly
accessible content may include personal data, such as your name or username in
connection with a social media profile. To the extent we obtain any such information,
we will maintain it in accordance with this Privacy Statement, and use it only
for the purposes described in this Privacy Statement.
How we share
your information
We may share your information:
With our affiliates and other companies in which we have an
economic interest or ownership rights.
With others working for us, which
includes third parties that perform services on our behalf such as running our
Site, sending communications for us, and executing marketing programs and
promotions.
With other third parties, such as
law enforcement or other government entities: (1) if we believe there has been
a violation of our Site policies; (2) if we believe that someone may be causing
injury to our rights or property, to other users, or to anyone else; (3) to
provide information to law enforcement; or (4) as required by law.
As part of a corporate restructure, such as a liquidation, reorganization, merger, sale of the company,
consolidation, change of control, asset or stock acquisition/disposition, or
other corporate combination. If that happens, we will use reasonable efforts to
make sure the transferee uses your information in a manner consistent with this
Privacy Statement.
We do not share your personal data with
any third-party vendor or website owner for their own marketing purposes.
Third-party
analytics
We may use third-party
providers to collect and analyze information about your use of the Site. These
providers may collect information about your online activities over time and
across third-party websites and other online services using cookies and other tracking
technologies discussed above in connection with your use of the Site. You may
be able to manage how these providers collect information by changing your
browser’s cookie settings.  Please
consult the What information
we collect about you section for more information about cookies. And remember that changes you make for one
browser won’t carry over to other browsers you use.
Some of the
analytics services we use are listed below. For information about how those
services collect and process data, click on the accompanying links. Please note
that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these third parties or
the content provided in their privacy statements.
Google
Analytics (www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)
Flurry (https://policies.oath.com/us/en/oath/privacy/index.html)
Adobe (https://www.adobe.com/privacy.html)
Crazy Egg (https://www.crazyegg.com/privacy, https://www.crazyegg.com/opt-out)
We participate in the Adobe Marketing Cloud Device Co-op
to better understand how you use our websites and apps across your devices, and
to deliver tailored advertising and marketing. Visit https://cross-device-privacy.adobe.com to learn more about the Adobe Marketing Cloud Device Co-op and to manage your choices
relating to this linking of devices.
If you have additional questions, you may contact us at the
address provided in the Contact us section below.
How you can control
your information
You may review and change any personal data in your account
profile and, where applicable, personal account preferences, stored in our
system if you believe it may be out of date or incorrect. And where you have
provided your consent for us to use your information, you may request to withdraw
that consent for future uses of your information. Where applicable, you may log
in to your account to update your information or preferences, which may include
revoking consent to certain communication outreach and marketing uses. You may
also contact us at the address provided in the Contact us section
below.
You may always opt out of receiving future commercial email or
text messages from us by following the opt-out instructions in emails or texts
we send you, or by contacting us at the address provided below. Please be
aware that if you opt out of receiving commercial messages from us, it may take
up to ten (10) business days for us to process your opt-out request, and you
may receive commercial messages from us during that period. Please note that if you opt out of future
text messages, this opt-out list is separate from our email preferences and
opt-out lists.
Even if you opt out
of receiving promotional and marketing material, we may still correspond with
you about your existing or past business relationships with us (e.g., any
purchase of our products or use of our services, or responses to your requests
for information either through the website or other means). We may also access
and view your information in the course of maintaining and improving the Site
and our services.
If you are a California resident, please consult the California
Privacy Rights section below for your rights and additional considerations. If
you are a Nevada resident, contact us here.
How we protect
your information
We have implemented technical, administrative, and physical
security measures designed to protect your personal data from unauthorized
access, disclosure, use, and modification. Although we strive to keep your
personal data secure, no security measures are absolute. Use caution when
transmitting personal data over the Internet.
Children’s personal
data
In light of the importance of protecting children's privacy, we do
not collect, process or use on our Site any information relating to an
individual whom we know to be under 13 years old without the prior, verifiable
consent of his or her legal representative. Such legal representative has the
right, upon request, to view the information provided by the child and/or to
require that it be deleted. Just contact us at the address provided in the Contact us section below.
Links to
third-party websites
We may provide
links to other websites maintained by unaffiliated third parties for your
convenience. But that should not be taken as our endorsement or approval of
those websites or their content. We do not maintain those third-party websites
and are not responsible for the availability, accuracy, or quality of their
content. We make no representations or warranties whatsoever about any other
website which you may choose to access through our Site. You should review the
terms and conditions related to the use of any third-party websites before
using them.
Changes to this
Privacy Statement
We may update this Privacy Statement
from time to time. When we do, we will post it on the Site and include the
effective date of the update. If there are material changes to our Privacy
Statement, we will post a prominent notice on our Site and provide other notice
as required by law.
Contact us
Bayer U.S. LLC
U.S. Office of Compliance – Data Privacy
100 Bayer Boulevard
Whippany, NJ 07981
Email
California Privacy Rights
Categories of personal data we
collect
We collect information that identifies, relates to,
describes, references, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could
reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular California consumer
or household (“personal data”). In particular, we have collected one or more
data types in the following categories of personal data from consumers within
the twelve (12) months preceding the effective date of this Privacy Statement:
Category
One or More Data
Types Collected?
A.
Identifiers such as a real name, alias, postal address, unique personal
identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address,
account name, social security number, driver’s license number, passport
number, or other similar identifiers.
Yes
B.
Any categories of personal data described in Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e),
such as name, signature, social security number, physical characteristics or
description, address, telephone number, passport number, driver’s license or
state identification card number, insurance policy number, education,
employment, employment history, bank account number, credit card number,
debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information,
or health insurance information.
Yes
C.
Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law.
Yes
D.
Commercial information, including records of personal property, products or
services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming
histories or tendencies.
Yes
E.
Biometric information, for example imagery of the iris, retina, fingerprint,
face, hand, palm, vein patterns, and voice recordings, from which an
identifier template, such as a faceprint, a minutiae template, or a
voiceprint, can be extracted, and keystroke patterns or rhythms, gait
patterns or rhythms, and sleep, health, or exercise data that contain
identifying information.
Yes
F.
Internet or other electronic network activity information, including, but not
limited to, browsing history, search history, and information regarding a
consumer’s interaction with an Internet Web site, application, or
advertisement.
Yes
G. Geolocation data.
Yes
H. Audio, electronic,
visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information.
Yes
I.  Professional or employment-related information.
Yes
J.  Non-public education information.
No
K.
Inferences drawn from any of the information identified in this subdivision
to create a profile about a consumer reflecting the consumer’s preferences,
characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes,
intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes.
Yes
For additional
information, see What
information we collect about you.
Categories of sources
of personal data
We obtain the categories of personal data listed above from
the following categories of sources:
Directly from our consumers (for example,
information provided through the Site, hardcopy forms, or other communications
with us).
From consumers’ activity on the Site (for
example, Site visit information collected directly or through third-party
analytics providers).
From a
device’s GPS, Wi-Fi, Bluetooth, or IP address.
From social
media, marketing partners, and other sources (for example, affiliates,
public and third-party databases, and other third parties).
For additional information, see What information we collect about you.
Our business
and commercial purposes for collecting personal data
We use the personal data we collect for our operational
purposes or other purposes set out in this Privacy Statement (see Why we
collect your information). Those purposes may include:
Auditing related to a current interaction with the
consumer and concurrent transactions, including, but not limited to, counting
ad impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning and quality of ad
impressions, and auditing compliance with this specification and other
standards.
Detecting security incidents, protecting against
malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, and prosecuting those
responsible for that activity.
Debugging to identify and repair errors that impair
existing intended functionality.
Short-term, transient use, provided the personal data
is not disclosed to another third party and is not used to build a profile
about a consumer or otherwise alter an individual consumer’s experience outside
the current interaction, including, but not limited to, the contextual
customization of ads shown as part of the same interaction.
Performing services on behalf of the business or
service provider, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing
customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying
customer information, processing payments, providing financing, providing
advertising or marketing services, providing analytic services, or providing
similar services on behalf of the business or service provider.
Undertaking internal research for technological
development and demonstration.
Undertaking activities to verify or maintain the
quality or safety of a service or device that is owned, manufactured,
manufactured for, or controlled by the business, and to improve, upgrade, or
enhance the service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or
controlled by the business.
In the twelve (12) months preceding the effective date of
this Privacy Statement, we have disclosed one or more data types in the
following categories of personal data of California consumers for a business
purpose:
Category A: Identifiers.
Category B: Categories
of personal data described in Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e).
Category C: Characteristics
of protected classifications under California or federal law.
Category D: Commercial
information.
Category E: Health or biometric information.
Category F: Internet
or other electronic network activity information.
Category G: Geolocation
data.
Category H: Audio,
electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information.
Category I: Professional
or employment-related information.
Category K: Inferences
drawn from other personal data.
We also use the personal data we collect for our commercial
or economic purposes, such as attracting consumers to buy, rent, lease, join,
subscribe to, provide, or exchange products, goods, property, information, or
services, or enabling or effecting, directly or indirectly, a commercial
transaction.
Categories of
third parties with whom we share personal data
For information on where we share personal data, see How we share your information.
In the twelve (12) months preceding the effective date of
this Privacy Statement, we have not sold personal data of California consumers.
Rights of California residents
If you are a California resident, you have the right to ask us
to send you the following information:
The
categories of personal data we have collected about you.
The
categories of sources from which we collected the personal data.
Our business
or commercial purpose for collecting personal data.
The
categories of third parties with whom we share personal data.
The specific
pieces of personal data the business has collected about you.
If you are a California resident, you have the right to ask us
to delete the personal data we have collected from you.
Non-discrimination
Your privacy rights are important. If you exercise your
privacy rights under California law, we will not do any of the following in
retaliation:
Deny
you goods or services.
Charge
you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through the
use of discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties.
Provide
you a different level or quality of goods or services.
Suggest
that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a
different level or quality of goods or services.
How California residents can
submit requests
If you are a California resident and you want to submit a request to us regarding your California rights, you or your authorized agent can contact us here, or
call us at 844-BAYER-DP (844-229-3737). You do not have to create an account
with us to submit a request.
We can only respond to your request if it is verifiable.
This means we are obligated to take reasonable steps to verify your identity
and your right to access the information you request. We may ask you to provide
additional information that will help us do so. We will only use that
additional information in the verification process, and not for any other
purpose.
We do not charge a fee to process or respond to your
verifiable consumer request unless it is excessive, repetitive, or manifestly
unfounded. If we determine that the request warrants a fee, we will tell
you why we made that decision and provide you with a cost estimate before
completing your request.
Search
Labels / MSDS
Absolute
Absolute Maxx
Admire Pro
Aliette
Alion
Autumn Super
Wolverine Advanced
BayerBayer GlobalBayer CropScience GlobalBayer Environmental ScienceGeneral Conditions of UsePrivacy StatementImprintCrop ProtectionOverviewFungicidesHarvest Aids / PGRHerbicidesInsecticidesSeedTraitsAll ProductsSeedGrowthOverviewAerisAllegianceEmesto SilverEverGolFluency Agent AdvancedGaucho 600Gaucho XTPoncho BetaRaxilThiramTrilexTrilex AdvancedSeed Treatment EquipmentResource CenterOverviewArticlesResearch and InnovationCereal ExpertsToolsReward ProgramsOverviewBayer PLUSInnovation Plus ProgramRoundup Ready PLUSWho We AreOverviewOur BusinessOur ValuesOur Locations News and EventsOur CommitmentOverviewAgVocateBee HealthFood Chain PartnershipGrow OnIntegrated Weed ManagementProduct StewardshipCalifornia Transparency in Supply ChainsView on Food LabelingBayer's Proposed Caldwell Canyon MineUS Roundup SettlementNews and EventsOverviewConnect BlogEventsAll NewsContact UsLast updated:December 9, 2019Copyright © Bayer CropScience
